<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Industry News on Parity Network</title><link>https://parity.uk/categories/industry-news/</link><description>Recent content in Industry News on Parity Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parity.uk/categories/industry-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How does Parity compare with Bristol Pound?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-23_how-does-parity-compare-to-the-bristol-pound/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-23_how-does-parity-compare-to-the-bristol-pound/</guid><description>How does Parity compare with Bristol Pound? We have been on a long journey of development to get to where we are today. I have personally been interested in alternative currencies for a while now. I have studied a wide range of models, from the famous Bitcoin, to Sardex, which is our main inspiration. The largest local currency in the UK is the Bristol Pound. I thought I would share some thoughts on how we differ from the UK’s leading local currency project.</description></item><item><title>An innovative financial model that supports sustainable development</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-16_an-innovative-financial-model-that-supports-sustainable-development/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-16_an-innovative-financial-model-that-supports-sustainable-development/</guid><description>An innovative financial model that supports sustainable development Sardex offers an interesting way to support sustainability Parity has been developed through studying different models around Europe, including Sardex in Sardinia. I originally went down this path looking for alternative financial mechanisms to support sustainable development. I initially was looking at the Bristol Pound, a local currency that gets a lot of positive media attention in the UK. Local currencies are often described as a model for supporting sustainable development.</description></item><item><title>Parity visits the annual Mitzas event in Sardinia and appears on Italian television</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-11-10_parity-visits-the-annual-mitzas-event-in-sardinia-and-appears-on-italian-television/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-11-10_parity-visits-the-annual-mitzas-event-in-sardinia-and-appears-on-italian-television/</guid><description>Parity visits the annual Mitzas event in Sardinia and appears on Italian television Parity is a business credit network that provides its users more trade and access to zero interest credit. The company is inspired by Sardex, which was originally set up in Sardinia, Italy in after 2008. In the ten years since Sardex’s initial creation, it has developed into a business credit network that has over 4500 users and had €40million worth of transactions in 2017.</description></item><item><title>HomeTown Plus and Countercoin - Community Development Programme</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-08_hometown-plus-and-countercoin-community-development-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-08_hometown-plus-and-countercoin-community-development-programme/</guid><description>HomeTown Plus and Countercoin - Community Development Programme Parity is developing a network that will allow small businesses to access zero interest finance and conduct more trade. The approach we are taking applies innovative financial technology within the West Midlands. We have been getting a huge amount of interest from national and international groups that recognise the potential for transacting in this way. This we had a call with Mike Riddell from Hometown Plus in Manchester, UK to discuss the project they are developing within their local business networks.</description></item><item><title>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</guid><description>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017 The BDCR Quarterly SME Finance Monitor has provided Government and private sector bodies an understanding of the SME credit market since 2011. Over 100,000 interviews with UK small business have now been conducted, at an average of 4500 each quarter. The aim of the reports to allow key interest groups to understand the state of the UK SME lending, UK SME credit and UK SME loans market.</description></item></channel></rss>