<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regional News on Parity Network</title><link>https://parity.uk/categories/regional-news/</link><description>Recent content in Regional News on Parity Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parity.uk/categories/regional-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Inclusive Economy</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-09-17_inclusive-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-09-17_inclusive-economy/</guid><description>Inclusive Economy The debate around what a ‘good change’ would look like for the economy has recently intensified. The coronavirus pandemic and the Black Lives Matter movement have both raised issues to which #BuildBackBetter and the Black Pound have proactively responded. Their positive and solution orientated approach cannot be ignored; Parity would like to support their effort in our locally community for a fairer and more sustainable change.
In this blog we will focus on inclusive economy - What is it?</description></item><item><title>Business Support for West Midlands Businesses</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-24_business-support-for-west-midlands-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-24_business-support-for-west-midlands-businesses/</guid><description>Business Support for West Midlands Businesses Starting a business can be liberating, however the journey to business growth and increased cashflow can be challenging. From the onset you may not have all the expertise or even the resources necessary for your business to prosper and thrive. Parity aims to support your growth offering a local network and an innovative cashflow solution.
Why is business support important?
Having the resources, youneed such as expertise, advice and access to finances from business supportservices can help boost the productivity of your company.</description></item><item><title>Parity explained through our first Birmingham transaction</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-15_parity-explained-through-our-first-birmingham-transaction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-15_parity-explained-through-our-first-birmingham-transaction/</guid><description>Parity explained through our first Birmingham transaction Parity is first business credit network within the UK and uses a model that has proven highly successful in Switzerland and Italy. Last Tuesday we had our launch in Brindley Place, Birmingham that was well attended by individuals and organisations from across the region. The event hosted a demonstration of our technology, but also provided guests an outline of how Parity works. We actually had our first transactions between two companies on our platform.</description></item><item><title>Launch of Parity in Birmingham</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-11_launch-of-parity-in-birmingham/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-11_launch-of-parity-in-birmingham/</guid><description>Launch of Parity in Birmingham UK’s first business credit network launched in the West Midlands
Parity hosted its launch event on Tuesday 9th of April at the NatWest Accelerator in Brindley Place, Birmingham. It was well attended by stakeholders from across the West Midlands who were interested in how Parity could help small businesses. We are the first business credit network in the UK and aim to support the regional economy.</description></item><item><title>ART Business Loans - Annual General Meeting</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-10-02_art-business-loans-annual-general-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-10-02_art-business-loans-annual-general-meeting/</guid><description>ART Business Loans - Annual General Meeting Parity Network was honoured to be invited along to the ART Business Loans AGM on Friday 28th September. The event was hosted at the newish iCentrum building on Innovation Birmingham Campus. The event is held every year and brings together members and wider stakeholders of ART Business Loans. The organisation, originally called Aston Reinvestment Trust, is a cooperative that was formed in 1997 with the explicit aim to address the funding gap experienced by small companies in the West Midlands.</description></item><item><title>Our talk at the Big Data Corridor Event at Innovation Birmingham Campus</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-13_our-talk-at-the-big-data-corridor-event-at-innovation-birmingham-campus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-13_our-talk-at-the-big-data-corridor-event-at-innovation-birmingham-campus/</guid><description>Our talk at the Big Data Corridor Event at Innovation Birmingham Campus Parity is a business credit network that will provide businesses within the West Midlands with more clients and access to a zero interest credit facility. We have been supported by the Innovation Engine project at Innovation Birmingham, the region&amp;rsquo;s leading digital and technology community. Yesterday I was given the opportunity to present Parity to a small group of that community to gage the initial reactions.</description></item><item><title>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</guid><description>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017 The BDCR Quarterly SME Finance Monitor has provided Government and private sector bodies an understanding of the SME credit market since 2011. Over 100,000 interviews with UK small business have now been conducted, at an average of 4500 each quarter. The aim of the reports to allow key interest groups to understand the state of the UK SME lending, UK SME credit and UK SME loans market.</description></item><item><title>Chancellor announces measures to address late payments for UK SMEs</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-15_chancellor-announces-measures-to-address-late-payments-for-uk-smes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-15_chancellor-announces-measures-to-address-late-payments-for-uk-smes/</guid><description>Chancellor announces measures to address late payments for UK SMEs Small businesses are the engine of the UK economy, making up over 90% of all businesses and employing over 60% of all private sector employees. However, small businesses have been often under served by different governments over the past four decades, with politicians focusing on supporting larger businesses. The banking crisis shook confidence in the large banks and a succession of corporate scandals have undermined the wider sectors.</description></item><item><title>MEBC Access to Finance Event</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-09_mebc-access-to-finance-event/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-09_mebc-access-to-finance-event/</guid><description>MEBC Access to Finance Event The Midlands Environmental Business Company is hosting a SME access to finance event in Birmingham, West Midlands. The event will help business owners decide what small business finance is available to SMEs in the region. National and regional studies consistently highlight that access to finance is one of the biggest barriers to growth for small businesses. SMEs find it difficult to access finance between £0-£150,000, even though companies of this size make up over60% of private sector employment and the UKs future prosperity hinges on SME innovation.</description></item><item><title>Launch of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-22_launch-of-the-midlands-engine-investment-fund/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-22_launch-of-the-midlands-engine-investment-fund/</guid><description>Launch of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund West Midlands businesses could benefit from greater access to finance Three funds have been launched that can provide a combined £100million worth of equity investment to businesses in the Midlands. The finance will join the wider offerings of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund and promoted by the Secretary of State Sajid Javid on 22nd February 2018. It will join a wider range of financial solutions, including debt and small business loans offered through the fund, which was originally launched by the British Business Bank.</description></item></channel></rss>