<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Birmingham Marketplace and Local Currency on Parity Network</title><link>https://parity.uk/</link><description>Recent content in Birmingham Marketplace and Local Currency on Parity Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parity.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A local currency to increase footfall for Birmingham restaurants and bars</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_a_local_currency_to_increase_footfall_for_birmingham_restaurants_and_bars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_a_local_currency_to_increase_footfall_for_birmingham_restaurants_and_bars/</guid><description>A local currency to increase footfall for Birmingham restaurants and bars Two local licensed premises are using Parity to attract new customers and increase their revenue Parity is a new digital marketplace for businesses within Birmingham that uses a local currency to boost liquidity amongst its users. We developed our platform working with a diverse range of companies in the Jewellery Quarter and support from the University of Birmingham and Birmingham and Solihull Local Enterprise Partnership.</description></item><item><title>A local currency to support digital and creative agencies to find new clients</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_a_local_currency_to_support_digital_and_creative_agencies_to_find_new_local_clients/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_a_local_currency_to_support_digital_and_creative_agencies_to_find_new_local_clients/</guid><description>A local currency to support digital and creative agencies to find new local clients Digital and creative businesses in the Jewellery Quarter are using Parity to connect to new customers and increase their revenue Parity is a new digital marketplace for businesses within Birmingham that uses a local currency to boost liquidity amongst its users. We developed our platform working with a diverse range of companies in the Jewellery Quarter and support from the University of Birmingham and Birmingham and Solihull Local Enterprise Partnership.</description></item><item><title>Use a local currency to meet new customers for your professional services business</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_use_a_local_currency_to_meet_new_customers_for_your_professional_services_business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-06-25_use_a_local_currency_to_meet_new_customers_for_your_professional_services_business/</guid><description>Use a local currency to meet new customers for your professional services business Local service firms are using Parity to meet new clients and increase their revenue Parity is a new digital marketplace for businesses within Birmingham that uses a local currency to boost liquidity amongst its users. We developed our platform working with a diverse range of companies in the Jewellery Quarter and support from the University of Birmingham and Birmingham and Solihull Local Enterprise Partnership.</description></item><item><title>Parity&#39;s response to coronavirus</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-18_paritys_response_to_coronavirus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-18_paritys_response_to_coronavirus/</guid><description>Parity&amp;rsquo;s response to coronavirus Parity will remain open for business and transactions during this outbreak. There is no service interruption expected. We will be working remotely during this social distancing phase. All of our technology is cloud based including our phone lines which can be answered away from the office.
It is our belief that Parity can help the Birmingham business community through this tough time. Either by providing the credit to be able to make purchases or by putting a business&amp;rsquo;s spare capacity to good use.</description></item><item><title>1000 trades networking club</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-13_1000-trades-networking-club/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-13_1000-trades-networking-club/</guid><description>1000 Trades Networking Club On Thursday the 5th March we hosted our first ‘1000 Trades Networking Club’; here are some highlights from the event.
It was a fantastic turnout and we are very thankful to everyone attending. It’s amazing to see how many businesses enjoy networking and want to trade more locally; that’s the kind of community we aim to build in the Jewellery Quarter.
&amp;ldquo;business that enjoy networking and want to trade more locally&amp;rdquo; We wish to give credit to 1000 Trades pub who made available the venue and tapped some great craft beers.</description></item><item><title>March Business Networking Events</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-28_march-business-networking-events/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-28_march-business-networking-events/</guid><description>Weekly Business Networking Events Tuesday Business for Breakfast - Two Greens Brunch Best Western Westley Hotel, 88 Westley Road, Acocks Green, B27 7UJ
Tuesday 6.45am or 10am
£8
Book
Wednesday Alliance BNI 70 Broad Street, Birmingham, B1 2HT
Wednesday 6.45am
Book
St.Paul BNI 14 St Paul&amp;rsquo;s Square, Birmingham, B3 1RB
Wednesday 6.45am
Book
Business for Breakfast - Castle Bromwich Castle Bromwich Hall Hotel, Chester Road, Birmingham, B36 9DE
Wednesday 7am</description></item><item><title>Why Parity? Benfits of using this local currency</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-21_why-parity-benefits-of-using-this-local-currency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-21_why-parity-benefits-of-using-this-local-currency/</guid><description>Why Parity? Benfits of using this local currency We acknowledge small independent businesses are the backbone of our economy and only by leveling the playing field we can let them drive local development and growth. We recognise the importance of competitiveness in the current economic fabric, but rather than advocate for more competition we support local cooperation and offer a tool that makes local trade more advantageous. Localism and entrepreneurship are two reasons why we have started Parity, but our members also have good economic reasons to use this local currency.</description></item><item><title>Parity supports four local firms to transact without cash</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-06_parity-supports-four-local-firms-to-transact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-06_parity-supports-four-local-firms-to-transact/</guid><description>Parity supports four local firms to transact without cash This week four businesses have used Parity to conduct transactions within our local currency. Parity is a B2B platform in Birmingham that has its own local currency. This week some of its members have had the first chance to really appreciate what Parity can do. It all started on Tuesday when Repc and Kinetic conducted their first transaction. It was supported by our broker and digital platform.</description></item><item><title>February Business Networking Events</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_february-business-networking-events/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_february-business-networking-events/</guid><description>Business Networking Monday 3rd February MaD Midlands - Make a Difference Networking Drinks
The Good Intent 32-33 Great Western Arcade Birmingham B2 5HU
5.30pm
Free
Book
Tuesday 4th February Cereal Network - Breakfast Networking
Alpha works, Alpha Tower, Suffolk Street Queensway, Birmingham, B1 1TT
7.30am - 9.30am
Free
Book
Speed Networking - Greater Birmingham Chamber of Commerce (GBCC)
Chamber House, 75 Harborne Road, Birmingham, B15 3DH
8.30am - 10.30am</description></item><item><title>Is Parity like Bitcoin?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_is-parity-like-bitcoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_is-parity-like-bitcoin/</guid><description>Is Parity like Bitcoin? A common question we get asked when we explain what Parity is is if it is like Bitcoin. Bitcoin is the most well known crypto currency and the first to gain any traction. Parity tries to solve a different problem to Bitcoin and therefore is quite different.
Bitcoin was developed by a pseudonymous person or group called Satoshi Nakamoto in 2008 to 2009. It borrowed ideas from previous projects such as Nick Szabo’s Bit Gold and Adam Back&amp;rsquo;s Hashcash as well proposing novel solutions to the problem of decentralised digital money.</description></item><item><title>How does Parity compare with Bristol Pound?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-23_how-does-parity-compare-to-the-bristol-pound/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-23_how-does-parity-compare-to-the-bristol-pound/</guid><description>How does Parity compare with Bristol Pound? We have been on a long journey of development to get to where we are today. I have personally been interested in alternative currencies for a while now. I have studied a wide range of models, from the famous Bitcoin, to Sardex, which is our main inspiration. The largest local currency in the UK is the Bristol Pound. I thought I would share some thoughts on how we differ from the UK’s leading local currency project.</description></item><item><title>Why is Parity a tool for Local Economic Resilience?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-10_why-is-parity-a-tool-for-local-economic-resilience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-10_why-is-parity-a-tool-for-local-economic-resilience/</guid><description>Why is Parity a tool for Local Economic Resilience? A currency designed to support independent businesses and boost the local economy is not a complete novelty mainly because of the long standing experience of the WIR Bank in Switzerland. Established in 1934 by Zurich’s entrepreneurs, WIR was conceived to address the lack of liquidity and credit crunch in years of economic depression.
The financial instability after 1929 made credit unavailable or very expensive, uncertainty reduced the overall consumption resulting in revenue losses; nevertheless the capacity of local businesses to produce and sell had not changed.</description></item><item><title>Parity app available in the app stores</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-11-25_parity-app-available-in-the-app-stores/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-11-25_parity-app-available-in-the-app-stores/</guid><description>Parity app available in the app stores Parity app is now available for both Android and iPhone. Search your app store for &amp;ldquo;Parity Network&amp;rdquo; to find it or alternatively follow the following links. You will need a to be a member of the parity network to use this app.
https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=network.parity.app
https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/parity-network/id1486679582</description></item><item><title>Why we use FreeAgent for our accounts software plus a referral code (49mrifmj)</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-11-14_why-we-use-freeagent-for-our-accounts-software-plus-a-referral-code-49mrifmj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-11-14_why-we-use-freeagent-for-our-accounts-software-plus-a-referral-code-49mrifmj/</guid><description>Why we use FreeAgent for our accounts software plus a referral code (49mrifmj) Previous to my time with Parity I had owned a web design company and a software contracting company. In this field FreeAgent is very popular as online accounts software as a replacement for either Sage / Quickbooks or a mix of spreadsheets provided by an accountant.
When starting Parity I knew that I wanted something similar for this business but assumed a “proper” business would need something more than FreeAgent which is really targeted to very small companies.</description></item><item><title>Visiting the Jewellery Quarter</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-10-25_visiting-the-jewellery-quarter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-10-25_visiting-the-jewellery-quarter/</guid><description>Visiting the Jewellery Quarter The Jewellery Quarter is a historical neighbourhood in the north west of Birmingham city center. In the 18th and 19th century it developed as an international hub for the jewellery industry and still nowadays it produces almost half of the jewellery made in the UK. Nevertheless, in the last decades this area of Birmingham has experienced a change. It has become residential area and home for many local and independent businesses.</description></item><item><title>Jewellery Quarter Pubs</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-10-16_jewellery-quarter-pubs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-10-16_jewellery-quarter-pubs/</guid><description>Jewellery Quarter Pubs 8 places to discover in the Jewellery Quarter Being part of the jewellery Quarter community has been great and we have quickly learnt that the Jewellery Quarter in Birmingham is a vibrant neighbourhood. In the morning people come here to work while In the evening - probably even from the afternoon -, people reach the Jewellery Quarter to enjoy nice food, a pint and, why not, some live music.</description></item><item><title>Ten things you must know about Parity</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-09-25_ten-things-you-must-know-about-parity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-09-25_ten-things-you-must-know-about-parity/</guid><description>Ten things you must know about Parity 1. What is Parity? Parity is a network for independent businesses in the Jewellery Quarter with its own local currency. Our digital platform facilitate networking and allows members to promote their business, connect with new local customers and increase revenue. Members can also benefit from using a local currency, called Parity, and accessing an interest free credit line to support cash flow and purchase expenses.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, w/c 12 of August.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-12_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-w-c-12-of-august/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-12_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-w-c-12-of-august/</guid><description>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, w/c 12 of August. Build relationships and engage with the local business community. Business networking in Birmingham is growing and you can find many opportunities for your business and your own development.
August is a quiet month for business networking in Birmingham and following will be listed the events available for next week, starting on Monday the 12th.
Monday 12th The week starts with a classic of the Greater Birmingham Chamber of Commerce (GBCC), the Curry Club Networking.</description></item><item><title>Type of Business Network &amp; Parity</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-02_type-of-business-network-parity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-02_type-of-business-network-parity/</guid><description>Type of Business Network &amp;amp; Parity Meet people and establish new relationships is important for everyone in business. In Parity we believe that entrepreneurs are stronger, more resilient and better off once they stay together within a network. Our platform innovates business networking’s idea using technology and delivering personalised and tailored services to the members.
Once you are deciding which network to join, it can be useful to look at the strength of its ties.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Event. w/c 29 of July 2019</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-26_business-networking-event-w-c-29-of-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-26_business-networking-event-w-c-29-of-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Event. w/c 29 of July 2019 Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands
Monday 29th of July Tech. Entrepreneurship 101 These are informal sessions covering business / entrepreneurship topics, looking at basic terminology and methodology with plenty of opportunity for discussion, Q&amp;amp;A, and hands-on work for your own venture plans.</description></item><item><title>Business Support for West Midlands Businesses</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-24_business-support-for-west-midlands-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-24_business-support-for-west-midlands-businesses/</guid><description>Business Support for West Midlands Businesses Starting a business can be liberating, however the journey to business growth and increased cashflow can be challenging. From the onset you may not have all the expertise or even the resources necessary for your business to prosper and thrive. Parity aims to support your growth offering a local network and an innovative cashflow solution.
Why is business support important?
Having the resources, youneed such as expertise, advice and access to finances from business supportservices can help boost the productivity of your company.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events w/c 22nd July 2019.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-19_business-networking-events-w-c-22nd-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-19_business-networking-events-w-c-22nd-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Events w/c 22nd July 2019. Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands.
Monday 22nd of July FREE 4 Day Business Start-up Workshop The programme is delivered by Award winning Business Advisors who run their own businesses and have many years experience in a wide range of industries.</description></item><item><title>Best Coworking Spaces Birmingham</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-16_best-coworking-spaces-birmingham/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-16_best-coworking-spaces-birmingham/</guid><description>Best Coworking Spaces Birmingham What is coworking? Are you looking for a new work space? Do you want to separate work from home? Tired of rummaging through busy Birmingham cafés for a seat for moment of focus? Or maybe you’re tired of the hefty expenses of long-term office leases? Are you looking for an environment that can help you unlock your full potential and inspire greater business productivity? Then coworking space in Birmingham may be perfect for you.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events in West Midlands w/c 15th July 2019.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-12_business-networking-events-in-west-midlands-w-c-15th-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-12_business-networking-events-in-west-midlands-w-c-15th-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Events in West Midlands w/c 15th July 2019. Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on business networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands.
Tuesday 16th of July 4N Sutton Coldfield – Business breakfast networking Friendly networking group that meets every Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, West Midlands.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-08_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-west-midlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-08_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-west-midlands/</guid><description>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, West Midlands. At Parity we believe in networking, not only as part of our business operations, but also as a way to improve ourselves and learn new things from other people. Luckily, the Birmingham area is rich with opportunities and you have the chance to engage in these business networking events over the course of the coming week.
Below are a list of events where you can attend to meet local entrepreneurs, and while your there why not meet someone from Parity and find more about this innovative business network.</description></item><item><title>How can Parity help grow your business?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-05-07_how-can-parity-help-grow-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-05-07_how-can-parity-help-grow-your-business/</guid><description>How can Parity help grow your business? An innovative platform to connect you to a new local market Parity offers small businesses a platform to access a new local market. It replicates highly successful networks in Italy and Switzerland, where 10,000s of businesses conduct €100millions of new trade each year. Parity connects you with new customers, opens up new trading opportunities and reduces your supply chain costs. It offers its members a zero interest credit facility, boosting liquidity and smoothing cash flow.</description></item><item><title>An innovative financial model that supports sustainable development</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-16_an-innovative-financial-model-that-supports-sustainable-development/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-16_an-innovative-financial-model-that-supports-sustainable-development/</guid><description>An innovative financial model that supports sustainable development Sardex offers an interesting way to support sustainability Parity has been developed through studying different models around Europe, including Sardex in Sardinia. I originally went down this path looking for alternative financial mechanisms to support sustainable development. I initially was looking at the Bristol Pound, a local currency that gets a lot of positive media attention in the UK. Local currencies are often described as a model for supporting sustainable development.</description></item><item><title>Parity explained through our first Birmingham transaction</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-15_parity-explained-through-our-first-birmingham-transaction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-15_parity-explained-through-our-first-birmingham-transaction/</guid><description>Parity explained through our first Birmingham transaction Parity is first business credit network within the UK and uses a model that has proven highly successful in Switzerland and Italy. Last Tuesday we had our launch in Brindley Place, Birmingham that was well attended by individuals and organisations from across the region. The event hosted a demonstration of our technology, but also provided guests an outline of how Parity works. We actually had our first transactions between two companies on our platform.</description></item><item><title>Launch of Parity in Birmingham</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-11_launch-of-parity-in-birmingham/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-04-11_launch-of-parity-in-birmingham/</guid><description>Launch of Parity in Birmingham UK’s first business credit network launched in the West Midlands
Parity hosted its launch event on Tuesday 9th of April at the NatWest Accelerator in Brindley Place, Birmingham. It was well attended by stakeholders from across the West Midlands who were interested in how Parity could help small businesses. We are the first business credit network in the UK and aim to support the regional economy.</description></item><item><title>Parity visits the annual Mitzas event in Sardinia and appears on Italian television</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-11-10_parity-visits-the-annual-mitzas-event-in-sardinia-and-appears-on-italian-television/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-11-10_parity-visits-the-annual-mitzas-event-in-sardinia-and-appears-on-italian-television/</guid><description>Parity visits the annual Mitzas event in Sardinia and appears on Italian television Parity is a business credit network that provides its users more trade and access to zero interest credit. The company is inspired by Sardex, which was originally set up in Sardinia, Italy in after 2008. In the ten years since Sardex’s initial creation, it has developed into a business credit network that has over 4500 users and had €40million worth of transactions in 2017.</description></item><item><title>ART Business Loans - Annual General Meeting</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-10-02_art-business-loans-annual-general-meeting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-10-02_art-business-loans-annual-general-meeting/</guid><description>ART Business Loans - Annual General Meeting Parity Network was honoured to be invited along to the ART Business Loans AGM on Friday 28th September. The event was hosted at the newish iCentrum building on Innovation Birmingham Campus. The event is held every year and brings together members and wider stakeholders of ART Business Loans. The organisation, originally called Aston Reinvestment Trust, is a cooperative that was formed in 1997 with the explicit aim to address the funding gap experienced by small companies in the West Midlands.</description></item><item><title>Our talk at the Big Data Corridor Event at Innovation Birmingham Campus</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-13_our-talk-at-the-big-data-corridor-event-at-innovation-birmingham-campus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-13_our-talk-at-the-big-data-corridor-event-at-innovation-birmingham-campus/</guid><description>Our talk at the Big Data Corridor Event at Innovation Birmingham Campus Parity is a business credit network that will provide businesses within the West Midlands with more clients and access to a zero interest credit facility. We have been supported by the Innovation Engine project at Innovation Birmingham, the region&amp;rsquo;s leading digital and technology community. Yesterday I was given the opportunity to present Parity to a small group of that community to gage the initial reactions.</description></item><item><title>West Midlands Combined Authority Social Economy Taskforce</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-09_west-midlands-combined-authority-social-economy-taskforce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-09-09_west-midlands-combined-authority-social-economy-taskforce/</guid><description>West Midlands Combined Authority Social Economy Taskforce Parity is developing a business to business mutual credit system that will launch in the West Midlands in 2019. Over the past six months we have been engaging with a wide range of stakeholders within the West Midlands. We have hoped to learn what the environment is like for small businesses, so we can ensure the service we are developing can best meet their needs.</description></item><item><title>What is Parity?</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-09_what-is-parity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-09_what-is-parity/</guid><description>What is Parity? What is it? Small businesses are the lifeblood of our modern economy. They make up 99% of all businesses in the UK and employ 60% of all workers. Small businesses are usually interested in taking on more clients and delivering more work. Unfortunately many of them find themselves overly reliant on big corporations for the chunk of their work. As seen in the West Midlands with the recent collapse of Carillion; when these fail, small companies and their employees are unduly affected.</description></item><item><title>HomeTown Plus and Countercoin - Community Development Programme</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-08_hometown-plus-and-countercoin-community-development-programme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-05-08_hometown-plus-and-countercoin-community-development-programme/</guid><description>HomeTown Plus and Countercoin - Community Development Programme Parity is developing a network that will allow small businesses to access zero interest finance and conduct more trade. The approach we are taking applies innovative financial technology within the West Midlands. We have been getting a huge amount of interest from national and international groups that recognise the potential for transacting in this way. This we had a call with Mike Riddell from Hometown Plus in Manchester, UK to discuss the project they are developing within their local business networks.</description></item><item><title>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-20_bdcr-group-sme-lending-report-q4-2017/</guid><description>BDCR Group SME Lending Report Q4 2017 The BDCR Quarterly SME Finance Monitor has provided Government and private sector bodies an understanding of the SME credit market since 2011. Over 100,000 interviews with UK small business have now been conducted, at an average of 4500 each quarter. The aim of the reports to allow key interest groups to understand the state of the UK SME lending, UK SME credit and UK SME loans market.</description></item><item><title>Chancellor announces measures to address late payments for UK SMEs</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-15_chancellor-announces-measures-to-address-late-payments-for-uk-smes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-15_chancellor-announces-measures-to-address-late-payments-for-uk-smes/</guid><description>Chancellor announces measures to address late payments for UK SMEs Small businesses are the engine of the UK economy, making up over 90% of all businesses and employing over 60% of all private sector employees. However, small businesses have been often under served by different governments over the past four decades, with politicians focusing on supporting larger businesses. The banking crisis shook confidence in the large banks and a succession of corporate scandals have undermined the wider sectors.</description></item><item><title>MEBC Access to Finance Event</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-09_mebc-access-to-finance-event/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-03-09_mebc-access-to-finance-event/</guid><description>MEBC Access to Finance Event The Midlands Environmental Business Company is hosting a SME access to finance event in Birmingham, West Midlands. The event will help business owners decide what small business finance is available to SMEs in the region. National and regional studies consistently highlight that access to finance is one of the biggest barriers to growth for small businesses. SMEs find it difficult to access finance between £0-£150,000, even though companies of this size make up over60% of private sector employment and the UKs future prosperity hinges on SME innovation.</description></item><item><title>The Development of Parity - Business Credit Network for the West Midlands</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-28_the-development-of-parity-business-credit-network-for-the-west-midlands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-28_the-development-of-parity-business-credit-network-for-the-west-midlands/</guid><description>The Development of Parity - Business Credit Network for the West Midlands West Midlands Business Credit Network Parity has evolved from a two year project researching a local currency for Birmingham, modelled on the Bristol Pound. The project provided the basis of a working group to explore the potential for an alternative currency in Birmingham. Research conducted included engaging with other local currency models in UK and European markets, allowing the project to fully understand the benefits and limitations for the initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Launch of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-22_launch-of-the-midlands-engine-investment-fund/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2018-02-22_launch-of-the-midlands-engine-investment-fund/</guid><description>Launch of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund West Midlands businesses could benefit from greater access to finance Three funds have been launched that can provide a combined £100million worth of equity investment to businesses in the Midlands. The finance will join the wider offerings of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund and promoted by the Secretary of State Sajid Javid on 22nd February 2018. It will join a wider range of financial solutions, including debt and small business loans offered through the fund, which was originally launched by the British Business Bank.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/1000trades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/1000trades/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/achut/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/achut/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/breslins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/breslins/</guid><description> Breslins</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/cloverhr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/cloverhr/</guid><description> Clover HR</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/greenfingers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/greenfingers/</guid><description>Jon White and Green Fingers Garden Services have been trading for a long time with a great history</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/iron-house/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/iron-house/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/kinetic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/kinetic/</guid><description> Kinetic Communications</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/little-media-agency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/little-media-agency/</guid><description> Little Media Agency</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/narce-media/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/narce-media/</guid><description> Narce Media</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/popcorn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/popcorn/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/repc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/repc/</guid><description> Repc</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/rock-and-roll-brewhouse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/rock-and-roll-brewhouse/</guid><description> Rock &amp;amp; Roll Brewhouse</description></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/stratum-now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/stratum-now/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/directory/telephone-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/directory/telephone-europe/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://parity.uk/privacy-and-data-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/privacy-and-data-policy/</guid><description>Privacy and data policy ul {list-style: disc} Privacy and Data Policy
Parity Network Ltd&amp;nbsp;is a company registered in England and Wales (company number 11236301) whose registered office is 84F Vyse Street, Jewellery Quarter, Birmingham, B18 6HA.
For the purpose of this document, when we refer to &amp;ldquo;Parity&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo; we are referring to Parity Network Ltd. When we refer to &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;clients&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;members&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;users&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;visitors&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;stakeholders&amp;rdquo; we are referring to any users of services provided by Parity Network Ltd.</description></item></channel></rss>