<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Networking Events on Parity Network</title><link>https://parity.uk/categories/networking-events/</link><description>Recent content in Networking Events on Parity Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parity.uk/categories/networking-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>August Business Networking Events</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-07-30_august-business-networking-events/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-07-30_august-business-networking-events/</guid><description>Tuesday 4th August Business Over Breakfast Birmingham Central Club
7.30am | FREE
Book | Zoom link
Saint Paul’s Networking Group 4:00pm - 5:00pm | FREE
Book
very Wednesday Business Network International St. Pauls BNI - Jewellery Quarter
6.45am
Book
Business Network International Alliance BNI - City Centre
7.30am
Book
Every Thursday Business Network International Apollo BNI - City Centre
6.45am
Book
Thursday 6th August The Business Network Virtual Networking Event</description></item><item><title>1000 trades networking club</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-13_1000-trades-networking-club/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-03-13_1000-trades-networking-club/</guid><description>1000 Trades Networking Club On Thursday the 5th March we hosted our first ‘1000 Trades Networking Club’; here are some highlights from the event.
It was a fantastic turnout and we are very thankful to everyone attending. It’s amazing to see how many businesses enjoy networking and want to trade more locally; that’s the kind of community we aim to build in the Jewellery Quarter.
&amp;ldquo;business that enjoy networking and want to trade more locally&amp;rdquo; We wish to give credit to 1000 Trades pub who made available the venue and tapped some great craft beers.</description></item><item><title>March Business Networking Events</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-28_march-business-networking-events/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-02-28_march-business-networking-events/</guid><description>Weekly Business Networking Events Tuesday Business for Breakfast - Two Greens Brunch Best Western Westley Hotel, 88 Westley Road, Acocks Green, B27 7UJ
Tuesday 6.45am or 10am
£8
Book
Wednesday Alliance BNI 70 Broad Street, Birmingham, B1 2HT
Wednesday 6.45am
Book
St.Paul BNI 14 St Paul&amp;rsquo;s Square, Birmingham, B3 1RB
Wednesday 6.45am
Book
Business for Breakfast - Castle Bromwich Castle Bromwich Hall Hotel, Chester Road, Birmingham, B36 9DE
Wednesday 7am</description></item><item><title>February Business Networking Events</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_february-business-networking-events/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2020-01-31_february-business-networking-events/</guid><description>Business Networking Monday 3rd February MaD Midlands - Make a Difference Networking Drinks
The Good Intent 32-33 Great Western Arcade Birmingham B2 5HU
5.30pm
Free
Book
Tuesday 4th February Cereal Network - Breakfast Networking
Alpha works, Alpha Tower, Suffolk Street Queensway, Birmingham, B1 1TT
7.30am - 9.30am
Free
Book
Speed Networking - Greater Birmingham Chamber of Commerce (GBCC)
Chamber House, 75 Harborne Road, Birmingham, B15 3DH
8.30am - 10.30am</description></item><item><title>Type of Business Network &amp; Parity</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-02_type-of-business-network-parity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-08-02_type-of-business-network-parity/</guid><description>Type of Business Network &amp;amp; Parity Meet people and establish new relationships is important for everyone in business. In Parity we believe that entrepreneurs are stronger, more resilient and better off once they stay together within a network. Our platform innovates business networking’s idea using technology and delivering personalised and tailored services to the members.
Once you are deciding which network to join, it can be useful to look at the strength of its ties.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Event. w/c 29 of July 2019</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-26_business-networking-event-w-c-29-of-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-26_business-networking-event-w-c-29-of-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Event. w/c 29 of July 2019 Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands
Monday 29th of July Tech. Entrepreneurship 101 These are informal sessions covering business / entrepreneurship topics, looking at basic terminology and methodology with plenty of opportunity for discussion, Q&amp;amp;A, and hands-on work for your own venture plans.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events w/c 22nd July 2019.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-19_business-networking-events-w-c-22nd-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-19_business-networking-events-w-c-22nd-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Events w/c 22nd July 2019. Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands.
Monday 22nd of July FREE 4 Day Business Start-up Workshop The programme is delivered by Award winning Business Advisors who run their own businesses and have many years experience in a wide range of industries.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events in West Midlands w/c 15th July 2019.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-12_business-networking-events-in-west-midlands-w-c-15th-july-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-12_business-networking-events-in-west-midlands-w-c-15th-july-2019/</guid><description>Business Networking Events in West Midlands w/c 15th July 2019. Business is made of human relationships and in Parity we believe these are stronger and more trust worthy at local level. Find out how Parity supports local market and follow our weekly blog on business networking events in Birmingham and West Midlands.
Tuesday 16th of July 4N Sutton Coldfield – Business breakfast networking Friendly networking group that meets every Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, West Midlands.</title><link>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-08_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-west-midlands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://parity.uk/posts/2019-07-08_business-networking-events-in-birmingham-west-midlands/</guid><description>Business Networking Events in Birmingham, West Midlands. At Parity we believe in networking, not only as part of our business operations, but also as a way to improve ourselves and learn new things from other people. Luckily, the Birmingham area is rich with opportunities and you have the chance to engage in these business networking events over the course of the coming week.
Below are a list of events where you can attend to meet local entrepreneurs, and while your there why not meet someone from Parity and find more about this innovative business network.</description></item></channel></rss>